workinsports.com 2015-05-12

# WorkInSports.com - Privacy Policy

**Work In Sports, LLC  
Last Updated: 3/2/2015  
**

This privacy policy applies to http://www.workinsports.com/ owned and operated by Work In Sports, LLC. This privacy policy describes how Work In Sports, LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site http://www.workinsports.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

Work In Sports, LLC ("WorkInSports.com") has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Web site, www.workinsports.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@WorkInSports.com](mailto:privacy@WorkInSports.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). 

**Dedicated to your privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. Our goal is to earn and keep your trust, according to the following principles: 

  * We will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes 
  * We will never share your contact information with a recruiter or hiring manager, unless both of you choose to contact one another regarding an open position 
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology 

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as your target job category, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy. 

Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. 

**Information We Collect and How We Use That Information**

Registration  
Our basic registration forms require users to provide contact information, including name, mailing address and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Should you choose to purchase services, your credit card information will be stored. We use this information for billing purposes only. If we have trouble processing your order, we will use your information to contact you. 

We will use your Personal Information for internal purposes only and will never sell or share your personal information with any third parties except as described in this privacy policy (see “Business Transitions”). Sensitive information such as your credit card information will be kept completely private and encrypted during collection and transmission to our credit card processors (see “Security”). 

Resume  
Should you post your resume, the amount of information you choose to keep confidential is entirely up to your discretion. You may enter as much or as little information as you choose. If you do not wish to reveal your contact information to hiring authorities, you may still post your resume as Confidential. All information posted will only be visible to recruiters and companies seeking employees. All recruiters are screened and have been determined by WorkInSports.com to be legitimately seeking applicants for open positions. 

Refer-A-Friend  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friends name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. WorkInSports.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

Your friend may contact Customer Support to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Target Job Information  
We also use Personal Information to provide you with targeted job information. For example, your email job alert will contain job information based on the job locations and categories you choose. 

Service Providers  
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer support. We use third parties to provide credit card processing services on our site. If you purchase service, we will share your personal information with this service provider to bill you for the services purchased. This service provider will only use your information to provide the services requested and will not use your information for any other purpose including their own marketing. This process is highly secure. 

Testimonials  
We post consumer testimonials on our Site. All testimonials in which Personal Information is included are always consented to prior to posting. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@WorkInSports.com](mailto:privacy@WorkInSports.com). 

Blog  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@WorkInSports.com](mailto:privacy@WorkInSports.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Keeping You Informed Through Email**

As a registered user of WorkInSports.com, you will automatically receive our service announcements (e.g., email address confirmation, signup confirmation, administrative messages, etc.) at your email address. Service announcements are required as they may contain information vital to your account; you may not unsubscribe from service announcements unless you deactivate your account. 

Job Alerts, Career Event Notification and Promotional are permission-based emails that will only be sent to you if you either opt-in at time of registration or turn them on in your account. You can update your email preferences by logging onto your “Account Settings” page. In addition, each permission-based email communication from us contains an unsubscribe link in the footer you can click to be instantly removed from that program. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

You can update your email preferences by logging onto your “Account Settings” page on the Site. In addition, each subscription-based email communication from us contains an unsubscribe link in the footer you can click to instantly remove yourself from the mailing list for that specific email subscription program. 

As a registered user of WorkInSports.com, you will automatically receive our service announcements (e.g., email address confirmation, signup confirmation, administrative messages, etc.) at your email address. Transactional communication is required as they may contain information vital to your account; you may not unsubscribe from service announcements unless you deactivate your account. 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or deactivate it by making the change on your “Account Settings” page or by contacting Customer Support. 

**Cookies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by WorkInSports.com and our [specify type e.g. marketing partners] partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for [our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication]. Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, our Web site may not function properly. 

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, and service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, and service providers use session ID cookies to enhance your web browsing experience. 

**Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We [do / do not] link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

**Local Storage Objects (Flash/HTML5)**

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. 

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

**Behavioral Targeting / Re – Targeting**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

WorkInSports.com has implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal Information. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our Web site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of WorkInSports.com. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warranty the security of any such Personal Information. 

**Links to Other Sites**

WorkInSports.com contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website over which we have no control and will bear no responsibility. Often these sites require you to enter your personal information as you apply for a job directly with the hiring company. We encourage you to read the privacy policy on all such Web sites as their policies may differ from ours. 

**Social Media**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Business Transitions**

In the event WorkinSports.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Access to Personal Information**

If your personal information or email changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your “Account Settings” page or by contacting Customer Support. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose your Personal Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WorkInSports.com. 

As such, we cannot ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties when compelled by law or to comply with legal process. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. 

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@WorkInSports.com](mailto:privacy@WorkInSports.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective. 

Work In Sports, LLC  
7010 East Chauncey Ln  
Suite 115  
Phoenix, AZ 85054
